const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"What is the cause of death in shaken baby syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Brain death","bool":true},{"option":"Cardiac arrythmia","bool":false},{"option":"Sepsis","bool":false},{"option":"Respiratory paralysis","bool":false},{"option":"Pontine hemorrhage","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which part of the kidney has the lowest osmolality?","answers":[{"option":"Collecting tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Proximal convoluted tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Tip of the loop of Henle","bool":false},{"option":"Descending limb of loop of Henle","bool":false},{"option":"Loop of Henle near distal tubule","bool":true}]},{"id":2,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Glucose is completely reabsorbed by the time filtrate reaches which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Distal tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Medullary collecting tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Cortical collecting tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Ascending limb of loop of Henle","bool":false},{"option":"Descending limb of loop of Henle","bool":true}]},{"id":3,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"What is the flow of plasma per minute into the Bowman's capsule called?","answers":[{"option":"Renal excretion rate","bool":false},{"option":"Volume of distribution","bool":false},{"option":"Reabsorption rate","bool":false},{"option":"Clearance","bool":false},{"option":"Glomerular filtration rate","bool":true}]},{"id":4,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"What is the treatment of severe hypokalemia?","answers":[{"option":"Insulin","bool":false},{"option":"Oral tablets with slow release","bool":false},{"option":"IV potassium in dextrose","bool":false},{"option":"IV potassium in normal saline","bool":true},{"option":"Phosphate binder","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which electrocardiogram (ECG) finding is common in hypokalemia?","answers":[{"option":"Wide QRS complex","bool":false},{"option":"P wave flattening","bool":false},{"option":"U waves","bool":true},{"option":"ST segment elevation","bool":false},{"option":"Hyperacute T waves","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which of the following structures is present entirely in the kidney cortex?","answers":[{"option":"Collecting tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Loop of henle","bool":false},{"option":"Pyramid","bool":false},{"option":"Calyx","bool":false},{"option":"Glomerulus","bool":true}]},{"id":7,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which of the following conditions is associated with a  tram-track appearance of glomerular basement membrane on electron microscopy?","answers":[{"option":"IgA nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":true},{"option":"Focal segmental glomerulosclerosis","bool":false},{"option":"Membranous nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Minimal change disease","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which organism is the most common cause of acute pyelonephritis?","answers":[{"option":"Pseudomonas aeroginosa","bool":false},{"option":"Staphylococcus aureus","bool":false},{"option":"Escherichia coli","bool":true},{"option":"Proteus mirabilis","bool":false},{"option":"Enterobacter","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"What portion of the cardiac output goes to the kidneys?","answers":[{"option":"8%","bool":false},{"option":"30%","bool":false},{"option":"5%","bool":false},{"option":"1%","bool":false},{"option":"20%","bool":true}]},{"id":10,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which one of these effects is observed in a flail chest?","answers":[{"option":"Increased AP diameter","bool":false},{"option":"Increased tidal volume","bool":false},{"option":"Subcostal recessions","bool":false},{"option":"Paradoxical breathing","bool":true},{"option":"Intercostal recessions","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which of the following fractures is seen in glancing bullet wounds to the head?","answers":[{"option":"Penetrating fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Comminuted fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Buckle fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Greenstick fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Gutter fracture","bool":true}]},{"id":12,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which of the following conditions is characterized by a spike and dome appearance of the glomerular basement membrane on electron microscopy?","answers":[{"option":"Rapidly progressive glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Membranous glomerulonephritis","bool":true},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Minimal change disease","bool":false},{"option":"Post-streptococcal glomerulonephritis","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"How does the medulla maintain a hyperosmolar gradient?","answers":[{"option":"Absorption of water","bool":false},{"option":"Action of Na/K/Cl co-transporter","bool":true},{"option":"Urea reabsorption through the proximal tubule","bool":false},{"option":"Epithelial sodium channels","bool":false},{"option":"Sodium chloride co-transporter","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which type of hypoxia is seen in cyanide poisoning?","answers":[{"option":"Hypemic","bool":false},{"option":"Histotoxic","bool":true},{"option":"Circulatory","bool":false},{"option":"Stagnant","bool":false},{"option":"Hypoxic","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"'Wire-loop' configuration of glomerular capillaries is seen in?","answers":[{"option":"IgA vasculitis","bool":false},{"option":"Lupus nephritis","bool":true},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Post-streptococcal glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Diabetic nephropathy","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which one of these is a contraindication for intravenous urography?","answers":[{"option":"Uremia","bool":false},{"option":"Congenital anomalies","bool":false},{"option":"Allergic to the contrast medium","bool":true},{"option":"Hematuria","bool":false},{"option":"Ureteric stone","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which one of these is not a type of proteinuria?","answers":[{"option":"Post-renal","bool":false},{"option":"Overflow","bool":false},{"option":"Tubular","bool":false},{"option":"Glomerular","bool":false},{"option":"Anatomical","bool":true}]},{"id":18,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which of these factors contribute to the intracellular shifting of potassium from the extracellular compartment?","answers":[{"option":"Adrenal insufficiency","bool":false},{"option":"Cell lysis","bool":false},{"option":"Insulin","bool":true},{"option":"Acidosis","bool":false},{"option":"Beta receptor antagonism","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which of these glomerular diseases is most common in children?","answers":[{"option":"IgA vasculitis","bool":false},{"option":"Membranoproliferative glomerulonephritis","bool":false},{"option":"Focal segmental glomerulosclerosis","bool":false},{"option":"Minimal change disease","bool":true},{"option":"Membranous nephropathy","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"Which type of hemorrhage is seldom fatal but plays a role in proving fatal when presented with other types of hemorrhages?","answers":[{"option":"Extradural hemorrhage","bool":false},{"option":"Subdural hemorrhage","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Pontine hemorrhage","bool":false},{"option":"Subarachnoid hemorrhage","bool":true},{"option":"Epidural hemorrhage","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2016","question":"A fracture in the middle cranial fossa can lead to reddish discoloration behind the ears. What is this called?","answers":[{"option":"Battle's sign","bool":true},{"option":"Raccoon's sign","bool":false},{"option":"Sunsetting sign","bool":false},{"option":"Phelp sign","bool":false},{"option":"McEwan's sign","bool":false}]}]
export default arr